Donny Cavalcante

Braga, Portugal



linkedin.com/in/donny-c-te



https://donnyc.netlify.app/



donny.cavalcante@student.curtin.edu.au



+1 (580) 203-2205

Summary

A creative Frontend Web Developer that has been designing digital experiences to improve customers´lives balancing goals. UX & creativity. He believes in collaborative working between designers and other parts of the company. Expect from him to always learn more about Web Development and UX/UI while creating and always pushing boundaries to deliver better products.

He is a passionate developer and He is an eternal learner about human behaviour.

Specialties: User Experience Design, User Interface Design, Visual Design, Design Thinking, and Frontend Web Development (HTML, CSS, and Javascript).

Experience



Freelance Web Developer

Self Employed

Aug 2020 - Present (1 month +)

Freelance web developer offering website and social marketing services to small - medium sized business around the wide world web.

Frontend Web Developer

ExodUX Design

Jan 2017 - Aug 2020 (3 years 8 months)

- Created wireframes and prototypes for web-based / mobile-based applications
- Designed applications, landing pages, email campaigns, and web ads
- Worked with front-end engineers to provide assets and web comps for development

Education



The Interaction Design Foundation

Front-End Developer (Career Path)





Curtin University

Bachelor of Arts - BA, Digital Experience 2018 - 2022

Licenses & Certifications



Membership Certificate - The Interaction Design Foundation



User Experience: The Beginner's Guide - The Interaction Design Foundation

78314-2020-394730



Digital Strategy - LinkedIn

- **Design Thinking: The Beginner's Guide** The Interaction Design Foundation 78314-2020-397411
- Become a UX Designer from Scratch The Interaction Design Foundation 78314-2020-427012

Skills

User Experience (UX) • Information Technology • Search Engine Optimization (SEO) • React.js • Responsive Web Design • Front-end Development • GitHub • SASS • Bootstrap • Adobe XD